Guide to the New Almaden Mine (Calif.) Collection, 1845-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VII: MAPS AND PLANS
  - FURNACES
    - Hopper slide, furnace #2, old #E3 & #362, 27x40 (Folder 15-12)
    - Hopper detail, old #E4, 27x34 2/3 (Folder 15-13)
    - Furnace #1, drawer doors and frames, old #E5, 1880; 15x19 2 (Folder 15-14)
    - Change of drawer #1, old #E7, 1880; 14x22.5 2/3 (Folder 15-15)
    - Side discharge for double title furnace, old #E8, 15x28 1/2 (Folder 16-1)
    - Top of furnace #1, old #E9, 1880; 8x31 3/4 (Folder 16-2)
    - Hopper for furnace #1, old #E10, 1879; 8x22.5 3/4 (Folder 16-3)
    - Hopper for furnace #1, old #E11, 1879; 10.5x11 1 1/2 (Folder 16-4)
    - Valves and slides in air chambers, furnace #1, old #E12, 1880; 11x26 3/4 (Folder 16-5)
    - Hopper with slide and frame, furnace #1, old #E13, 1879; 35.5x36 1 1/2 (Folder 16-6)
    - Furnace #1, old #E14, 8x15 3/16 (Folder 16-7)
    - Furnace #1, general plans, old #E15, 35x76 (Folder 16-8)
    - Furnace #1, first sketch, cottage in Chinese quarter sketch by CH on verso, old #E17, ca. 1890; 29x33 1/2 (Folder 16-9)
    - Furnace #1, different views, old #E18, 1880; 34x54 1/2 (Folder 16-10)
    - Furnace #2, cast iron plates, old #E19, 1879; 13x14.5 3 (Folder 16-11)
    - Furnace #2, details, old #E20, 1879; 27x38.5 1 1/2 (Folder 16-12)
    - Furnace #2, condenser pipes, old #E22, 1879; 24x29 3/4 (Folder 16-13)
    - Furnace #2, connecting pipe, old #E23, 1879; 18x35.5 1 1/2 (Folder 16-14)
    - Granzita furnace #2, back air chamber valves and slides, old #E24, 1880; 18x27.5 1/2 (Folder 16-15)
    - Hopper construction, furnace #2, Sulphur Banks Mining Co. old #E25, 1879; 18.5x25 1 (Folder 17-1)
      Heynemann
    - Elevations, furnace #2, old #E26, 1879; 25x34 1/2 (Folder 17-2)
      Haste
    - Elevations, originally for furnace #1, old #E27, 1879; 33.5x35.5 1/2 (Folder 17-3)
    - Elevations, originally for furnace #1, old #E28, 1880; 33x34 1/2 (Folder 17-4)
    - Condensers and fans for furnace #1, old #E29 & #359, 36x58.5 (Folder 17-5)
    - Flue for furnaces #1 & #2, old #E30, 1880; 36x56 1/2 (Folder 17-6)
    - Tierras for furnace #3, old #F1, 27x44 3/4 (Folder 17-7)
    - Tierras for furnace #3, old #F2, 29.5x42 3/4 (Folder 17-8)
    - Tierras for furnace #3, old #F3, 25.5x43 3/4 (Folder 17-9)
    - Furnace #3, elevations, old #F5, 25.5x43 3/4 (Folder 17-10)
    - Furnace #3, elevation and plan, old #F6, 23x31 3/4 (Folder 17-11)
    - Furnace #3, elevation, old #F7, 1877; 9x28 1/4 (Folder 17-12)
      H.J. Huttner
    - Tierra and granzita roasting furnace #3, old #F8, 1877; 17x24 1/4 (Folder 17-13)
    - Furnace #3, elevations, old #F9, 1880; 36x50 3/4 (Folder 17-14)
    - Furnace #3, plan and elevations, old #F10, 1877; 22x33 1/4 (Folder 17-15)
    - Furnace #3, #8, old #F11, 15.5x36 1/4 (Folder 18-1)
    - Furnace #3, #8, old #F12, 17.5x30 (Folder 18-2)
    - Furnace #3, #8, top of furnace, old #F13, 1879; 12x36 1 1/2 (Folder 18-3)
    - Furnace #3, #8, plan of hoppers, sketch, old #F14, 25x38 (Folder 18-4)
    - Furnace #3, #8, plan of hoppers, finished drawing, old #F15, 15x40 (Folder 18-5)
    - Furnace #3, #8, plan of hoppers, finished drawing, old #F16, 25x38 (Folder 18-6)
    - Furnace #3, #8, plan of hoppers, finished drawing, old #F17, 12x35 1/4 (Folder 18-7)
    - Furnace #3, #8, plan of hoppers, finished drawing, old #F18, 13x35 1 1/2 (Folder 18-8)
    - Furnace #3, #8, plan of hoppers, finished drawing, old #F19, 23x36 1 1/2 (Folder 18-9)
    - Furnace #3, #8, mid and end hopper, old #F20, 14x38 3 (Folder 18-10)
    - Furnace #3, #8, slide valves for hoppers, old #F21, 1873; 22x34 1 1/2 (Folder 18-11)
    - Furnace #3, #8, bed plate and girder, old #F22, 1877; 22x28 3/4 (Folder 18-12)
    - Furnace #3, #8, top plates, old #F23, 1877; 20x28 3/4 (Folder 18-13)
    - Furnace #3, #8, top plates, old #F24, 1877; 20x28 3/4 (Folder 18-14)
    - Furnace #3, #8, sheet iron casing, old #25, 1877; 24x31 3/8 (Folder 18-15)
    - Furnace #3, #8, sheet iron casing, old #F26, 1877; 24x31 3/8 (Folder 19-1)
    - Furnace #3, #8, foundation plan, old #F27, 1877; 30x31 3/4 (Folder 19-2)
    - Furnace #3, #8, slides, old #F28, 1878; 26.5x39.5 3 (Folder 19-3)
    - Furnace #3, #8, slides, old #F29, 1878; 25x38 3 (Folder 19-4)
    - Furnace #3, #8, slides, old #F30, 1878; 25x38 3 (Folder 19-5)
    - Furnace #3, #8, slides, old #F31, 1878; 27x39.5 3 (Folder 19-6)
    - Furnace #3, #8, slides, old #F32, 1878; 27x36.5 3 (Folder 19-7)
    - Furnace #3, beams, old #F33, 26.5x40 (Folder 19-8)
    - Furnace #3, throat, pencil, old #F35 & #356, 26.5x40 (Folder 19-9)
    - Furnace #3, top, detail of hopper, old #F38, 27x40 (Folder 19-10)
    - Detail of hopper, old #F36, 15x43 (Folder 19-11)
    - Furnace #3, discharge car, old #F39, 20x28 1 1/2 (Folder 19-12)
    - Furnace #3, furnace cars, old #F40, 15x26.5 1 1/2 (Folder 19-13)
    - Outlet pipe, doors, hopper, ashpit valve, old #F41, 1877; 18x25 3/4 (Folder 19-14)
    - Outlet pipe, color, old #F42, 1877; 19x26 3/4 (Folder 19-15)
    - Channel doors for #3, approved by Fiedler, 1877; 11.5x29.5 (Folder 20-1)
    - Valves and slide back air chamber, old #F44, 1880; 11x31 3/4 (Folder 20-2)
    - Outlet pipes, old #F45, 24x38 1/2 (Folder 20-3)
    - Shaking tables, old #F47, 1877; 22x28 3/4 (Folder 20-4)
    - Shaking tables, color, old #F48, 1877; 22x28 3/4 (Folder 20-5)
    - Detail of shaking tables, old #49, 1878; 15x30 3 (Folder 20-6)
    - Furnace #3, details, old #F50, 1878; 15x26 (Folder 20-7)
    - Details with shaking table, old #F51, 1878; 15x26 (Folder 20-8)
    - Shaking tables, old #F52, 1880; 25x35 3/4 (Folder 20-9)
    - Dust accumulator, old #F53, 11x25.5 1 1/2 (Folder 20-10)
    - Furnace #3, heater condenser, old #F54, 1880; 9.5x20 1 1/2 (Folder 20-11)
    - Furnace #5, elevations with attachments, old #F55, 1879/1880; 22.5x35.5 1/2 (Folder 20-12)
    - Furnace #5, hopper, old #F56, 24x37 1 1/2 (Folder 20-13)
    - Furnace #5, hopper, color, old #F57, 17x36.5 (Folder 20-14)
    - Furnace #5, #3, iron condenser, old #F58, 1880; 23.5x36 1/4 (Folder 20-15)
    - Furnace #5, general plan, old #F59, 1878; 22.5x28 3 (Folder 21-1)
    - Furnace #5, hopper, old #F61, 7.5x20.5 1/16 (Folder 21-2)
    - Furnace #6, elevations, old #F62, 24.5x37 3/8 (Folder 21-3)
    - Furnace #1, sections, old #F63, 24.5x37.5 3/8 (Folder 21-4)
    - Furnace #1, condenser walls, old #F64, 30x60 1/4 (Folder 21-5)
      Fiedler
    - Furnace #3, dryer to connect with condenser, old #F65, 8.5x29 (Folder 21-6)
    - Furnace #8, old #G2, 1876; 25x32 1 1/2 (Folder 21-7)
    - Furnace #8, old #G6 & #665, 1876; 13x23 (Folder 21-8)
      Gyurkovitz
    - Furnace #8, hopper, with sketch of bay window, old #G7, 1880; 27x40 1 1/2 (Folder 21-9)
    - Furnace #8, hopper, with sketch of bay window, color, old #G8, 21.5x40 1 1/2 (Folder 21-10)
    - Furnace #8, ensemble of hoppers, with note by RRB, old #G9, 1880; 18x18.5 1 1/2 (Folder 21-11)
    - Furnace #8, alterations, old #G10, 1880; 26.5x35.5 3/4 (Folder 21-12)
    - Bedplate #8, top view, old #G12 & #353, 28.5x57 3/4 (Folder 21-13)
    - Bedplate #8, top view, side view, old #G15, 24x38 3/4 (Folder 21-14)
    - Furnace #8, 3 sections of the sheet iron covering, old #G17, 24.5x37 3/4 (Folder 21-15)
    - Furnace #8, 4th section of the sheet iron covering, old #G19, 24.5x38.5 3/4 (Folder 22-1)
    - Furnace #8, Girders, stands and frames for sliding doors, old #G23., 1876; 23x36.5 1 1/2 (Folder 22-2)
    - Frames for sliding doors for new furnace, old #G25, 1876; 22x37 1 1/2 (Folder 22-3)
    - Shaking tables for tierra furnace, old #G28 & #669, 1876; 28x42 1 1/2 (Folder 22-4)
    - Furnace #8, shaking tables, discharge cars, old #G29, 24x36.6 1 1/2 (Folder 22-5)
    - Furnace #8, shaking tables, discharge cars, old #G30, 23x41 1 1/2 (Folder 22-6)
    - Shaking tables, old #32, 1876; 22x28 1 1/2 (Folder 22-7)
    - Truck for discharge cars, old #G37, 1876; 14.5x14.5 1 1/2 (Folder 22-8)
    - Furnace #8, drying floor and dampers on on soot towers, old #G43, 22x34 3/4 (Folder 22-9)
    - Furnace #8, drying floor and dampers on on soot towers, old #G45, 1876; 13x29.5 3/4 (Folder 22-10)
    - Furnace #9, continuous iron clad coarse ore, old #H1, 1877; 14x23 (Folder 22-11)
    - Furnace #9, sketches, old #H2, 1877; 11x22 (Folder 22-12)
    - Furnace #7, iron clad, old #H3, 1874; 25.5x39 3/4 (Folder 22-13)
    - Iron clad furnace #7 & #9, general plan, old #H7, 28.5x46 3/4 (Folder 22-14)
    - Furnace #9, iron clad furnace, old #H8, 30x42.5 (Folder 22-15)
    - Furnace #9, iron clad furnace, old #H10, 30x42 3/4 (Folder 23-1)
    - Plan and profile of iron clad furnace, old #H11, 1874; 14x30 1/4 (Folder 23-2)
    - Furnace #8 & #9, old #H12, 1877; 24x33 (Folder 23-3)
    - Iron clad furnace, old #H13, 1879; 24x34.5 1/2 (Folder 23-4)
      J.A. Haste
    - Furnace mounting, old #H16, 1874; 20x28 3/4 (Folder 23-5)
    - Furnace mounting, old #H17, 1874; 20x30 3/4 (Folder 23-6)
    - Furnace #9, plan of pipes, furnace #7 on verso, old #H19, 1876; 20x28 3/4 (Folder 23-7)
    - Furnace #2, proposed escape pipes from iron clad furnace, 1875; 18x24 3/4 (Folder 23-8)
    - Furnace #7, framework for shed, old #H23, 1876; 21x22 1/4 (Folder 23-9)
    - Furnace #9, framework for shed, old #H24, 1876; 15x26.5 1/4 (Folder 23-10)
    - Furnace #9, ground plan of shed, old #H25, 1875; 21x22 1/4 (Folder 23-11)
    - Furnace #7 & #9, ground plan and profile, old #H27, 20.5x31 (Folder 23-12)
    - Furnace #7, iron clad furnace and condensing system, 2 pieces, old #H29 & 666, 7x16, 18x18 (Folder 23-13)
    - Bischoff's generator, old #I1, 1879; 27x37 1 (Folder 23-14)
    - Bischoff's generator, copy of plate from German mining book, old #I2, 9x14.75 1/2 (Folder 23-15)
      Kunde
    - Roasting furnace as built by Perschbacher, Napa City, old #I3, 1879; 19x26 1/2 (Folder 24-1)
    - Letter, from La Grange Ditch and Hydraulic mining Co., 1879; 7.25x10 (Folder 24-2)
    - Furnace plan and elevations, Pope Valley, old #I4, 1879; 16.5x20 3/4 (Folder 24-3)
      C. Fitzgerald
    - Plans and elevations for working gold and silver ore separating company process, lithograph, old #I5, 19x24 1/4 (Folder 24-4)
      E. Fletcher
    - Old lime kiln with 3 fireplaces, Ruedersdorf, Prussia, plate from a book, old #I6, 1879; 30x32.5 1/4 (Folder 24-5)
      L. Heynemann
    - Plan of iron clad furnace and framework for shed, old #I7, 14x50 (Folder 24-6)
    - Knox's furnace, copy from tracing by J.A. Haste, 1873, old #I11 & #357, 1879; 43x50 1/2 (Folder 24-7)
    - Knox's furnace, old #I12, 1879; 30x30.5 1/4 (Folder 24-8)
    - Furnace, Eplay, old #I13, 24x35/5 (Folder 24-9)
    - Elevations and plan of furnace Eplay, old #I15, 15x30 4 (Folder 24-10)
    - Huttner and Scott roasting furnace, old #I16, 1877; 22x30 3/8 (Folder 24-11)
      Huttner and Scott
    - Shaking table, old #I17, 1877; 20.5x30 3/4 (Folder 24-12)
    - Sheet iron casing for furnace, old #I18, 1877; 20.5x24.5 3/8 (Folder 24-13)
    - Bed plate girder outlet pipe and door frames, old #I19, 1877; 26x27.5 3/4 (Folder 24-14)
    - Top plates and hopper, old #I20, 1877; 25x27.5 3/4 (Folder 24-15)
    - Pencil sketch for continuous tierra furnace, old #I25, 1880; 15x18 1/4 (Folder 25-1)
      Randol
    - Janin's Quicksilver furnace, old #I23, 27x37 1/2 (Folder 25-2)
      Louis Janin
    - Proposed furnace #10, pencil sketch, old #124 & #354, 1880; 36x58 3/8 (Folder 25-3)
    - Pencil sketch for continuous tierra furnace, old #125, 1880; 34.5x36 3/16 (Folder 25-4)
    - Quicksilver furnace, old #I27, 1875; 29x51 1/2 (Folder 25-5)
    - Promotional poster for lime roasting furnace, old #I29, 1874; 14.5x22.5 1/2 (Folder 25-6)
      Sampson and Beardsley
    - Sections and elevations of unidentified furnaces, old #I30, 26x26 (Folder 25-7)
    - Shaft furnace, old #I31, 24x24.5 1/2 (Folder 25-8)
    - Janin furnace, Brooklyn, N.Y., old #I33, 1879; 16.5x16.5 3/8 (Folder 25-9)
    - Janin furnace, Brooklyn, N.Y., old #I34, 16.5x20.5 3/8 (Folder 25-10)
    - Different system of tierras for furnaces with 2 lithos attached, old #I35, 16.5x28.5 (Folder 25-11)
    - Copy of Defts exhibit 46, old #I36, 26x39.5 (Folder 25-12)
    - Unidentified, Figure 1, old #I37, 15x20 (Folder 25-13)
    - Lithograph illustration from German book, plate 1, old #I38, 12.5x18.5 (Folder 25-14)
    - Chalkburning furnace, illustration from German book, plate 2, old #I39, 12.5 x 18.5 (Folder 25-15)
    - Illustration from German book, plate 3, old #I40, 12.5x19 (Folder 26-1)
    - Illustration from German book, plate 4, old #I41, 12.5 x 18.5 (Folder 26-2)
    - Open ceiling coalburning roasting furnace, plate 16, old #I42, 12.5 x 18.5 (Folder 26-3)
    - Dry chamber, old #J3, 19x30 3/8 (Folder 26-4)
    - Condensing chambers, joint of roof plates, old #J5, 45x46 1/2 (Folder 26-5)
    - Water tank for condensing pipes for furnace #7 & #9, old #J6, 1881; 26x36 1 (Folder 26-6)
    - Furnaces #7 & #9, condensers, pencil sketch, old #J8 & 355, 1881; 34x47.5 (Folder 26-7)
    - Furnaces #7 & #9, condensers, pencil sketch, old #J9, 1881; 29x37.5 (Folder 26-8)
    - Furnaces #7 & #9, condensers, pencil sketch, pipes, old #J10, 1881; 23.5x29 (Folder 26-9)
    - Furnaces #7 & #9, blueprint, old #J11, 1883; 16x26 (Folder 26-10)
    - Furnace #8, condenser, old #J13, 24.5x33 3/8 (Folder 26-11)
    - Furnace #8, condenser, old #J14, 24x30 3/8 (Folder 26-12)
    - Furnace #8, position of condensers with water cooling, old #J15, 1880; 19x19 3/16 (Folder 26-13)
    - Furnace #8, condenser pipes with additions, old #16, 1888; 8x14.5 3/8 (Folder 26-14)
    - Furnace #8, condenser pipes, old #J17, 1880; 10x16 3/8 (Folder 26-15)
    - Furnace #8, condenser, pipes, old #J19, 10.5 x 20.5 3/16 (Folder 27-1)
    - Furnace #8, one new brick condenser and 4 new wood condensers no longer in existence, 1880, old #J20, 1879; 13.5x15 3/16 (Folder 27-2)
      H.J.Huttner
    - Furnace #3, condensers, old #J21, 25x38 1/4 (Folder 27-3)
    - Furnace #1 & #2, arrangement of condenser furnaces, old #J22, 1880; 18x27.5 3/16 (Folder 27-4)
    - Furnace #2, condensers, old #J23, 1880; 10x15.5 (Folder 27-5)
    - Furnace #1, condensers, old #J24, 1880; 10.5x16 (Folder 27-6)
    - Furnace #1, condensers, old #J25, 1880; 10x14 3/16 (Folder 27-7)
    - Furnace #1, condenser pipes and tank, old #J27, 1880; 16.5x23 1/6 (Folder 27-8)
    - Condenser, old #J30, 1882; 18x20 1 1/2 (Folder 27-9)
    - Randol's Quicksilver condenser, including patent sketch, old #J32, 10x15 (Folder 27-10)
    - Randol and Fiedler's patent quicksilver condenser, old #J33, 1874; 20x27 1 (Folder 27-11)
      I. Cash
    - Randol and Fiedler's patent quicksilver condenser, old #J34, 1874; 19x25 1/2 (Folder 27-12)
    - Wood condensers, pencil sketch, old #J35, 23x29 1/2 (Folder 27-13)
    - Furnace #1, #2, & #3, wood condenser, old #J36, 1880; 25x31 3 (Folder 27-14)
    - Longitudinal section of condenser and ground plan, old #J37, 20x27 1/2 (Folder 27-15)
    - Longitudinal section of condenser and ground plan, old #J38, 25x29 (Folder 28-1)
    - Randol and Fiedler's patent quicksilver condenser, old #J39, 24x36 1/2 (Folder 28-2)
    - Randol and Fiedler's patent quicksilver condenser, old #J40, 24x36 1/2 (Folder 28-3)
    - Vertical section of air shaft, old #J41, 1874; 15x21 2 (Folder 28-4)
      I.C.J.
    - Furnace #3, Rowe and Johnson's condensing tower, old #J42, 1874; 15x21 1/2 (Folder 28-5)
    - Furnace #2, drip rock rack and plan of V boxes, old #J43, 1874; 15x21 2/3 (Folder 28-6)
    - Furnace #1, upper top and bottom water boxes, old #J44, 1874; 15x21 1/3 (Folder 28-7)
    - Condenser pipes with pencil notes by Huttner, 2 pieces, old #J47, 1880; 11x11.5 1 1/3 (Folder 28-8)
    - Framing plan of 2 condensers 5 feet apart, old #J48, 25x25 (Folder 28-9)
    - Blueprint plan of furnace yard, old #367, 1879; 25x39 30 (Folder 28-10)
    - Blueprint plan of furnace yard, old #367, 1879; 25x39 30 (Folder 28-11)
    - Blueprint plan of furnace yard, old #367, 1879; 25x39 30 (Folder 28-12)
    - Furnaces and condensers, old #368, 1890; 25x39 8 (Folder 28-13)
    - Furnaces and condensers, old #368, 1890; 25x39 8 (Folder 28-14)
    - Furnaces and condensers, old #368, 1890; 25x39 8 (Folder 28-15)
    - Furnaces and condensers, old #368, 1890; 25x39 8 (Folder 29-1)
    - Furnaces and condensers, old #368, 1890; 25x39 8 (Folder 29-2)
    - Furnaces and condensers, old #368, 1890; 25x39 8 (Folder 29-3)
    - Furnace plan, old #369, 1917; 18.5x21 50 (Folder 29-4)
      C.B. Sloan & Company
    - Furnace #1, trap door and details, old #NN1, 1880; 22.5x37 1 (Folder 29-5)
    - Furnace #1, handles of slides, old #NN2, 1879; 36x43 (Folder 29-6)
    - Furnace #1, handles of slides, old #NN2, 1879; 26x33.5 2/3 (Folder 29-7)
    - Furnace #1, with corrections, note from JBR, 1879; 36x56 2/3 (Folder 29-8)
    - Furnace #3, outlet pipes, old #NN4, 27x41 2 (Folder 29-9)
    - #8 hydraulic elevator, water tank hoist on verso, old #NN7, 1879; 15x23.5 (Folder 29-10)
      William Gray
    - Cross section, front, side, vertical elevations of unidentified furnace or blower, old #NN8, 7.5x20 (Folder 29-11)
    - Guadalupe tierra furnace sketch, old #NN9, 8x10 (Folder 29-12)
    - Sketch of unidentified furnace, 2 pieces, old #NN10, 7.5 x 11.5 (Folder 29-13)
      J.A. Brown
    - Study of discharges for double granzita furnaces, old #NN11, 1880; 25.5x36 4/3 (Folder 29-14)
      Hagemeier
    - New Herreshoff furnace, Pacific Foundry Co., blueprint, old #NN12, 11.5x18 (Folder 29-15)
    - Furnace #7, condenser, old #NN13, 33x43 2 (Folder 30-1)
    - Furnace #8, ore skip, old #NN14, 1876; 11.5x16 2/3 (Folder 30-2)
    - Iron clad furnace, partial profile, old #NN15, 8x12 (Folder 30-3)
    - Quicksilver reduction plant with new Herreshoff roasting furnace, Senator, old #654, 21.5x32 4 (Folder 30-4)
    - Iron clad shaft furnaces, 12x14.5 8 (Folder 30-5)
    - Iron clad shaft furnaces, 13x14.5 8 (Folder 30-6)
    - Iron clad shaft furnaces, 13x14.5 8 (Folder 30-7)
    - Iron clad shaft furnaces, 13x14.5 8 (Folder 30-8)
    - Iron clad shaft furnaces, 13.25 x 14 8 (Folder 30-9)
    - Iron clad shaft furnaces, 13x14 8 (Folder 30-10)
    - Furnace, 1876; 29x43 (Folder 30-11)
    - Furnace #6, proposed alteration, old #325, 15x37 (Folder 30-12)
    - Furnaces, Alamitos Creek, roads, 9x12.75 (Folder 30-13)
    - Furnace B, 19x25.5 (Folder 30-14)
    - Treater drawings A, 1916; 24.5 x 25.5 (Folder 30-15)
    - Condenser, blueprint, old #B28, 6.25x13 (Folder 31-1)
    - Iron clad shaft furnace, 11.75 x 14.5 8 (Folder 31-2)
  - CENTRAL STOPE
    - Main Tunnel to Relief Tunnel, Profile, old #102, 19x30.5 (Folder 31-3)
    - Main Tunnel to Day Tunnel, section showing dip of vein, old #104, 1875; 22x31 80 (Folder 31-4)
    - Vertical Section, Day Tunnel, Great Eastern Road, old #108, 17x28 (Folder 31-5)
    - Mine Hill Stopes, Main Shaft, old #110, 16.5x18 (Folder 31-6)
    - Mine Hill Stopes, Main and Junction Shafts, old #110A, 12.5x13 (Folder 31-7)
    - Mine Hill Stopes, Including Far West, old #110B, 14x16.5 (Folder 31-8)
    - Upper Velasco, Juan Vega, A. Morales Drift, old #111, 12.5x25 30 (Folder 31-9)
    - Main Shaft, 600 Junction, Far West cross section, old #137, 21.5x24 (Folder 31-10)
      United States Geological Survey
    - Vertical Plane Mine Hill, Main Tunnel to New (Day) Tunnel, section 1, old #184, 1864; 19x54 60 (Folder 31-11)
      Day
    - Vertical Plane Mine Hill, Day Tunnel, section 2 old #192, 1864; 18x64 60 (Folder 31-12)
    - Mine Hill Summit to Buenos Ayres, vertical plane, old #193, 1864; 19x54 60 (Folder 31-13)
    - Velasco, Great Eastern, Santa Rita, Theatre, color coded, old #200, 21x27 40 (Folder 31-14)
      Reade?
    - Velasco, Santa Rita West, old #201, 26.5x36 40 (Folder 31-15)
    - Santa Rita section, Far West cross section 600, #2 to Junction, old #219B, 12x14 20 (Folder 32-1)
      Schneider?
    - Santa Rita cross section, 50' Bench Mine Hill, old #219D, 1942; 22.5x35 40 (Folder 32-2)
      Martin, CNS
    - Mine Hill, Upper Tunnels, old #219F, 8.5x10 80 (Folder 32-3)
    - Mine Hill, elevations, old #219G, 1943; 15.25 x 25.25 40 (Folder 32-4)
      CNS
    - Mine Hill, vertical stopes, photo enlargement, old #219H, 18x22.5 40 (Folder 32-5)
      Martin
    - Mariquita Shaft, cross section, old #219I, 12.5 x 12.5 40 (Folder 32-6)
    - Santa Rita, Great Eastern 600-650 section, old 219J, 1943; 5.5 x 12.5 40 (Folder 32-7)
    - Far West 600 Main and Junction shafts, old #219N, 1946; 30x39 40 (Folder 32-8)
    - El Collejio, old #219P, 1943; 14.5x18 (Folder 32-9)
    - Main Shaft?, 700 level, raises and chutes, old #219Q, 1943; 8.5x11 (Folder 32-10)
    - Santa Rosa, Far West to Santa Rita, old #219T, 1967; 24x36 40 (Folder 32-11)
      Martin, C.N. Schuette
    - Santa Rosa, colored, old #219T, 1967; 24x36 40 (Folder 32-12)
    - Santa Rosa, Warren Stope, 600-800 levels, blueprint, old #409, 23x29 40 (Folder 32-13)
    - Santa Rosa, incline 800 level, Santa Clara #1, old #425, 1877; 26x37 20 (Folder 32-14)
      Browne
    - Juan Vega Workings, 8.5x35 40 (Folder 32-15)
    - Main Tunnel, 1100-200 level, color, 1965; 28x36 40 (Folder 33-1)
    - 3 vertical sections through Mine Hill, see Wisser's report 1941, 28x36 100 (Folder 33-2)
    - Great Santa Rita, La Ardilla, Velasco, Santa Catarina, blueprint of old map, 22.5x30 (Folder 33-3)
    - Great Santa Rita, La Ardilla, Velasco, Santa Catarina, blueprint of old map, 22.5x30 (Folder 33-4)
    - Great Santa Rita, La Ardilla, Velasco, Santa Catarina, blueprint of old map, 22.5x30 (Folder 33-5)
    - Santa Rita Area, 14x19 (Folder 33-6)
    - Plan of Works Above Main Tunnel Near Main Shaft, San Francisco, Plan of the underground works, blueprint, 22x36 80 (Folder 33-7)
    - Mine Hill trenching, 10.5x10.75 60 (Folder 33-8)
    - Tunnel plan, Santa Rita West, Great Santa Rita, 18x24.5 (Folder 33-9)
    - Tunnel plan, Upper Velasco, Lower Velasco, Day Tunnel, 18.25x24.25 (Folder 33-10)
    - Tunnel plan, Far West, El Collegio, 18x24 (Folder 33-11)
    - Tunnel plan, Relief, Santa Clara, 18x24 (Folder 33-12)
    - New Santa Rita West, Goldsworthy crosscut, 18x24 (Folder 33-13)
    - Tunnel plan, La Ardilla, La Cruz, Main Tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 33-14)
    - Layout of areas, major tunnels, Far West, Great Santa Rita, Main Tunnel, La Ardilla, El Collegio, 42x60 (Folder 33-15)
    - Forrest King, Central Lode, old #335, 20x26.5 (Folder 34-1)
    - Tunnel plan, Main Tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 34-2)
    - Tunnel plan, Great Santa Rita, Marysville, La Ventura, 24x18.25 (Folder 34-3)
  - HARRY, SANTA MARIANA, VELASCO, VICTORIA
    - Harry Tunnel, Upper NW and China Dump Underground, old #63, 18x26 40 (Folder 34-4)
    - Harry Tunnel, 500-600 levels and stopes, old #64, 16x33.5 (Folder 34-5)
    - Composite, Harry Workings, Plate 1, blueprint, old #90, 1944; 35x37 40 (Folder 34-6)
    - Harry 500, West Branch, old #95A, old #H20, 18x24 40 (Folder 34-7)
    - Composite, Harry Workings and Machine Stope, 1944; 32x37 50 (Folder 34-8)
    - Yellow Kid, 1943; 20.5x36 40 (Folder 34-9)
    - Santa Mariana, surface to 400, old #471, 1900; 30x36 40 (Folder 34-10)
    - Santa Mariana, workings, compiled from notes by GDE, pencil, 19.5x28 40 (Folder 34-11)
      Eberlein?
    - Santa Mariana, underground, Eberlein's best guess, 22x36 (Folder 34-12)
      Eberlein
    - Top of Mine Hill, vertical section and Velasco to 800, old #106, 1876; 18x37 80 (Folder 34-13)
      Von Leicht?
    - Top of Mine Hill, vertical section and Velasco, San Francisco, old #107, 1880; 28x43 80 (Folder 34-14)
    - Top of Mine Hill, vertical section and Velasco, San Francisco, old #107, 1880; 28x43 80 (Folder 34-15)
    - Bush, Prospect, Robles Tunnels, pencil, old #199, 1910?; 23.5x31 (Folder 35-1)
    - Velasco to Theatre, old #219A, 19x23 20 (Folder 35-2)
    - Velasco to Theatre, with additions, old #219V, 1967; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 35-3)